UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup III: Office of the President, 1971-1997; 3; 35.20
  - Series 5: Projects/Subjects -- John M. Reilly [RESTRICTED], 1978 June-1993 October; 1987 June-1993 May; 3.5; 16.0
    - New York State Economic Development [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box III.5.8, Folder 2)
    - NYS Ethics Commission-Financial Disclosure Statement-Exemption Request Application-Academic Employees [RESTRICTED], 1989 March 17 (Box III.5.8, Folder 3)
    - NYS Ethics Commission-Financial Disclosure Statement-Exemption Request Application-Professional Employees [RESTRICTED], 1989 March 17; 3 folders (Box III.5.8, Folder 4-6)
    - NYS Ethics Commission-Financial Disclosure Statement-Job Titles [RESTRICTED], 1989 April-1989 May; 2 folders (Box III.5.8, Folder 7-8)
    - New York State Ethics Commission [RESTRICTED], 1989 May-1989 June; 1992 January-1993 April (Box III.5.8, Folder 9)
    - New York State Ethics Commission (folder created during processing with selected additional materials from Associate Director of Staff file) [RESTRICTED], 1988 September-1990 September (Box III.5.8, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear Waste [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box III.5.8, Folder 11)
    - Nurses & Public Policy conference (March 1990) [RESTRICTED], 1989 October-1989 December (Box III.5.8, Folder 12)
    - Nursing Profession Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box III.5.8, Folder 13)
    - Nursing Profession Work Group [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box III.5.8, Folder 14)
    - NYSUT Committee of 100 [RESTRICTED], 1991 February 26; 1991 May 13-1991 May 14 (Box III.5.8, Folder 15)
    - NYSUT Committee of 100 [RESTRICTED], 1992 February 24-1992 February 25 (Box III.5.8, Folder 16)
    - NYSUT Committee of 100 Lobby Day [RESTRICTED], 1992 May 19 (Box III.5.8, Folder 17)
    - NYSUT Committee of 100 Lobby Day [RESTRICTED], 1993 February 22-1993 February 23 (Box III.5.8, Folder 18)
    - NYSUT Community College Conference [RESTRICTED], 1991 October (Box III.5.8, Folder 19)
    - NYSUT Community College Conference, October 1992 [RESTRICTED], 1992 April (Box III.5.8, Folder 20)
    - NYSUT Correspondence and Communications [RESTRICTED], 1990-March 1993 (Box III.5.8, Folder 21)
    - NYSUT Endorsements and Oppositions [RESTRICTED], 1988-1990 (Box III.5.8, Folder 22)
    - NYSUT Endorsements 1992-Letters of Thanks and Acknowledgment from Endorsees [RESTRICTED], 1992 August-1992 December (Box III.5.8, Folder 23)
    - NYSUT endorsements 1992-NYSUT Presidents Conference on Endorsements [RESTRICTED], 1992 January-1992 July; 2 folders (Box III.5.8, Folder 24-25)
    - NYSUT Higher Ed Lobby Day [RESTRICTED], 1992 March 10 (Box III.5.8, Folder 26)
    - NYSUT Higher Ed Lobby Day [RESTRICTED], 1993 March 02 (Box III.5.8, Folder 27)
    - NYSUT-Local Presidents Conference [RESTRICTED], 1993 April (Box III.5.9, Folder 1)
    - NYSUT New Local Presidents' Conference [RESTRICTED], 1989 May-1989 July (Box III.5.9, Folder 2)
    - NYSUT New Local Presidents' Conference [RESTRICTED], 1990 May-1990 June (Box III.5.9, Folder 3)
    - NYSUT Positive Negotiations Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1990 April (Box III.5.9, Folder 4)
    - NYSUT-Unity Caucus Executive Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 December (Box III.5.9, Folder 5)
    - NYSUT-UUP-specific materials from NYSUT Board of Directors meetings [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box III.5.9, Folder 5A)
    - Occupational Health Clinical Center, Central New York [RESTRICTED], 1987 July-1987 September (Box III.5.9, Folder 6)
    - Officers Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box III.5.9, Folder 7-8)
    - Officers (and UUP office particularly Employee Benefits Specialists) [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1988 June (Box III.5.9, Folder 9)
    - Officers (and UUP office particularly Employee Benefits Specialists) [RESTRICTED], 1988 July-1989 September (Box III.5.9, Folder 10)
    - Officers (and UUP office particularly Employee Benefits Specialists) [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1991 November (Box III.5.9, Folder 11)
    - Organizing [RESTRICTED], 1992 August-1993 May (Box III.5.9, Folder 12)
    - Organizing-Michigan Technological University [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1993 April (Box III.5.9, Folder 13)
    - Organizing-State University Research Foundation [RESTRICTED], 1992 August-1993 March (Box III.5.9, Folder 14)
    - Parking Negotiations/Fees [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1989 December (Box III.5.9, Folder 15)
    - Parking Negotiations/Fees [RESTRICTED], 1990 January-1990 March (Box III.5.9, Folder 16)
    - Parking Negotiations/Fees [RESTRICTED], 1990 March-1990 August (Box III.5.9, Folder 17)
    - Pay Equity [RESTRICTED], 1989 August-1991 October (Box III.5.9, Folder 18)
    - Pedagogy/Enrollment [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box III.5.9, Folder 19)
    - Performance Measures [RESTRICTED], 1993 February (Box III.5.9, Folder 20)
    - Political Campaigns 1992 [RESTRICTED], 1992 July-1992 October (Box III.5.9, Folder 21)
    - Post-Secondary Instruction, Institute of (proposed legislation) [RESTRICTED], 1988; 1990 (Box III.5.9, Folder 22)
    - Potsdam-Student Grievance Process/Grade Appeals [RESTRICTED], 1986 March-1987 October (Box III.5.9, Folder 23)
    - Professional Development and Quality of Work Life (PDQWL) Committee [RESTRICTED], 1986 June-1987 January (Box III.5.9, Folder 24)
    - Professional Development and Quality of Work Life (PDQWL) Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 February-1987 June (Box III.5.9, Folder 25)
    - PDQWL Grant/Leonard Kastle "Passion of Mother Ann" [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box III.5.9, Folder 26)
    - PDQWL Grant/Leonard Kastle "Passion of Mother Ann" [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box III.5.9, Folder 27)
    - Professional Life Quality Survey, Potsdam [RESTRICTED], 1988 April-1988 May (Box III.5.9, Folder 28)
    - Professionals-Professional Newer Members Survey Results [RESTRICTED], 1993 May (Box III.5.9, Folder 29)
    - Professionals-Reclassification [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box III.5.9, Folder 30)
    - Professionals-Reclassification and Promotion [RESTRICTED], 1987 May-1987 August (Box III.5.9, Folder 31)
    - Professionals-Reclassification and Promotion [RESTRICTED], 1987 August-1987 October (Box III.5.9, Folder 32)
    - Professionals-Reclassification and Promotion [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1988 January (Box III.5.9, Folder 33)
    - Public Employee Division (NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1987 July-1988 January; 2 folders (Box III.5.10, Folder 1-2)
    - Public Employee Division, NYS AFL-CIO (miscellaneous) [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box III.5.10, Folder 3)
    - Public Employee Division (NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1988-1990 (Box III.5.10, Folder 4)
    - Public Employee Division Advisory Board agendas and minutes (NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1988-1990 (Box III.5.10, Folder 5)
    - Public Employee Division Advisory Board (NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1990 March (Box III.5.10, Folder 6)
    - Public Employee Division (NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1991 April-1993 May (Box III.5.10, Folder 7)
    - Public Employee Division (NYS AFL-CIO), Pension Reform [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1989 December (Box III.5.10, Folder 8)
    - Public Employee Pension Task Force (Public Employee Division NYS AFL-CIO) [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box III.5.10, Folder 9)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1987 May-1987 December (Box III.5.10, Folder 10)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 August (Box III.5.10, Folder 11)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1988 August-1988 December; 2 folders (Box III.5.10, Folder 12-13)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1988 December-1989 December; 6 folders (Box III.5.10, Folder 14-19)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1990; 2 folders (Box III.5.10, Folder 20-21)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund - Board of Trustees Meeting (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 29 (Box III.5.10, Folder 22)
    - Public Employees Benefit Fund - Board of Trustees Meeting (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 29 (Box III.5.11, Folder 1)
    - Public Employee Benefit Fund [RESTRICTED], 1991 December-1992 October (Box III.5.11, Folder 2)
    - Public Employee Federation (PEF) [RESTRICTED], 1987 July; 1991 October-1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 3)
    - Re-Imagine UUP [RESTRICTED], 1991 September-1992 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 4)
    - Re-Imagine UUP [RESTRICTED], 1992 June-1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 5)
    - Reclassification-Counseling Psychologists [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box III.5.11, Folder 6)
    - Regents-NY State Education Department [RESTRICTED], 1987 July-1987 August (Box III.5.11, Folder 7)
    - Regents-NY State Education Department [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 December (Box III.5.11, Folder 8)
    - Regents, New York State [RESTRICTED], 1983 May; 1987 June-1992 December (Box III.5.11, Folder 9)
    - Regional Budget Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1988; 1989; 1993 (Box III.5.11, Folder 10)
    - Regional Budget Meetings-Handouts [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1989 March (Box III.5.11, Folder 11)
    - Regional Meetings-Promotion, Compensation, Classification of Professionals [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box III.5.11, Folder 12)
    - Reilly, John M., biographical information [RESTRICTED], 1989-1993 (Box III.5.11, Folder 13)
    - Reilly Talks-"Bargaining for Professionalism: A Union Vision of the Future" 16th Annual Conference-National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions [RESTRICTED], 1988 April-1988 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 14)
    - Reilly Talks-Comments on AP Tests/College-Bound Minority Students [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1990 January (Box III.5.11, Folder 15)
    - Reilly Talks-"Content and Quality of Training" New York State Job Training Partnership Council-State Leadership Team's Informational Roundtable on Content and Quality of Education for Adults [RESTRICTED], 1989 March-1989 April (Box III.5.11, Folder 16)
    - Reilly Talks-Federation of Maryland Teachers Quest Conference and Convention on "Quality Educational Standards in Teaching" [RESTRICTED], 1989 November (Box III.5.11, Folder 17)
    - Reilly Talks-Four Union Unity Rally [RESTRICTED], 1991 February 05 (Box III.5.11, Folder 18)
    - Reilly Talks-"Funding Higher Education in New York", APSCUF [RESTRICTED], 1990 March 17 (Box III.5.11, Folder 19)
    - Reilly Talks-L/M Contract Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 December 01 (Box III.5.11, Folder 20)
    - Reilly Talks-Miscellaneous, including UUP meetings/conferences [RESTRICTED], 1989-1991 (Box III.5.11, Folder 21)
    - Reilly Talks-"Professional Values in Faculty Promotion" (Washington Federation of Teachers) [RESTRICTED], 1989 April (Box III.5.11, Folder 22)
    - Reilly Testimony-Albany Common Council, Omnibus Human Rights Law, November 12 [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.11, Folder 23)
    - Reilly Testimony-Committee on University Revenue and Tuition Policy, Board of Trustees, State University of New York [RESTRICTED], 1990 December 07 (Box III.5.11, Folder 24)
    - Reilly Testimony-Assembly Republican Task Force-The Future of the State University of New York [RESTRICTED], 1993 March 10 (Box III.5.11, Folder 25)
    - Reilly Testimony-Assembly Standing Committee on Higher Education [RESTRICTED], 1987 June 18 (Box III.5.11, Folder 26)
    - Reilly Testimony-Assembly Standing Committee on Higher Education [RESTRICTED], 1991 November 19 (Box III.5.11, Folder 27)
    - Reilly Testimony-Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1991 February 11 (Box III.5.11, Folder 28)
    - Reilly Testimony-New York State Ethics Commission [RESTRICTED], 1988 October 18 (Box III.5.11, Folder 29)
    - Reilly Testimony-Regents Committee on Higher and Professional Education [RESTRICTED], 1992 September 16 (Box III.5.11, Folder 30)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 January 25 (Box III.5.11, Folder 31)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 January 30 (Box III.5.11, Folder 32)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1990 January 29 (Box III.5.11, Folder 33)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1992 January 28 (Box III.5.11, Folder 34)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee on State Operations Budget [RESTRICTED], 1993 February 02 (Box III.5.11, Folder 35)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate and Assembly Committees on Higher Education, Senate Finance Committee and Assembly Ways and Means Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989 December 19 (Box III.5.11, Folder 36)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Higher Education Committee on SUNY Admission Criteria [RESTRICTED], 1991 May 08 (Box III.5.11, Folder 37)
    - Reilly Testimony-Senate Higher Education Committee [RESTRICTED], 1992 May 13 (Box III.5.11, Folder 38)
    - Reilly Testimony-Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 May 12 (Box III.5.11, Folder 39)
    - Reilly Statement-"Colleagues Still: A Statement on Elimination of Mandatory Retirement in Colleges and Universities", AFT Advisory Commission on Higher Education [RESTRICTED], 1992 March 11 (Box III.5.11, Folder 40)
    - Reilly Statement-Differential Tuition for SUNY University Centers-Statement in Opposition [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box III.5.11, Folder 41)
    - Reilly Statement-Draft memo to State re: "Let's Have an Accounting" regarding cuts in the budget [RESTRICTED], 1991 December 06 (Box III.5.11, Folder 42)
    - Reilly Statement-"Keepin' on Keepin' On: Updating a Sketch for the UUP Strategic Plan or 'The Long Haul' Revisited", presented at the Fall 1992 DA [RESTRICTED], 1992 September (Box III.5.11, Folder 43)
    - Reilly Statement-"The Long Haul: A Sketch for a UUP Strategic Plan for a Strong Union in a Comprehensive University", presented at Spring 1992 DA [RESTRICTED], 1992 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 44)
    - Reilly Statement-Sexual Harassment [RESTRICTED], 1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 45)
    - Reilly Statement-Tenure [RESTRICTED], 1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 46)
    - Release Time Review Committee [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box III.5.11, Folder 47)
    - Research Regulations/Misconduct Guidelines (re: research in science) [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1988 July (Box III.5.11, Folder 48)
    - Research Regulations/Misconduct Guidelines (re: research in science) [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1990 January (Box III.5.11, Folder 49)
    - Retirement [RESTRICTED], 1988 December; 1991 October-1992 January; 1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 50)
    - Retirement, Early (including incentive programs) [RESTRICTED], 1990 June-1991 August; 2 folders (Box III.5.11, Folder 51-52)
    - Retirement, Early (including incentive programs) [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1992 October; 2 folders (Box III.5.11, Folder 53-54)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program in SUNY-background materials (1963-1964) on establishment of [RESTRICTED], 1992 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 55)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program, Temporary Task Force on/Suspension of State TIAA-CREF Contributions (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box III.5.11, Folder 56)
    - Retirement: Optional Retirement Program, Temporary Task Force on/Suspension of State TIAA-CREF Contributions (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1993 May (Box III.5.12, Folder 1)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1991 May-1992 January (Box III.5.12, Folder 2)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 January-1992 February (Box III.5.12, Folder 3)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1992 March (Box III.5.12, Folder 4)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 April-1992 May (Box III.5.12, Folder 5)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 August; 1993 January-1993 February (Box III.5.12, Folder 6)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs including meeting agendas, minutes, and handouts [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 June (Box III.5.12, Folder 7)
    - Retirement: Temporary Task Force on Optional Retirement Programs including meeting handouts [RESTRICTED], 1992 May-1992 June (Box III.5.12, Folder 8)
    - Retirement: TIAA-CREF [RESTRICTED], 1991 February-1993 February (Box III.5.12, Folder 9)
    - Retrenchments 1990-91 [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box III.5.12, Folder 10)
    - Retrenchments 1991-92 [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992 (Box III.5.12, Folder 11)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box III.5.12, Folder 12)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1988; 2 folders (Box III.5.12, Folder 13-14)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box III.5.12, Folder 15)
    - Safety and Health [RESTRICTED], 1989 August-1993 May (Box III.5.12, Folder 16)
    - Safety and Health in the Workplace-UUP compilation of background information [RESTRICTED], 1988 April (Box III.5.12, Folder 17)
    - SASU (Student Association of the State University) [RESTRICTED], 1989 December; 1993 January-1993 February (Box III.5.12, Folder 18)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1989 Campaign [RESTRICTED], 1989 December-1990 April (Box III.5.12, Folder 19)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1991 Campaign/Loaned Executive Program [RESTRICTED], 1991 February-1992 February; 2 folders (Box III.5.12, Folder 20-21)
    - SEFA (State Employee Federated Appeal)-1992 Campaign [RESTRICTED], 1992 February-1993 March (Box III.5.12, Folder 22)
    - Sexual Harassment [RESTRICTED], 1990 February-1993 May (Box III.5.12, Folder 23)
    - Solidarity-UUP South Africa Labor Support Fund [RESTRICTED], 1990 January (Box III.5.12, Folder 24)
    - Solidarity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1987 November-1988 August (Box III.5.12, Folder 25)
    - Solidarity Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 September-1993 May (Box III.5.13, Folder 1)
    - Student Recruitment and Retention Committee [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1990 May (Box III.5.13, Folder 2)
    - SUNY 5 Year Plans [RESTRICTED], 1980; 1989 (Box III.5.13, Folder 3)
    - SUNY 1985 Flex Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1985 July (Box III.5.13, Folder 4)
    - SUNY 1987-1988 Financial Plan [RESTRICTED], 1987 August (Box III.5.13, Folder 5)
    - "SUNY 2000" [RESTRICTED], 1991 August-1991 September (Box III.5.13, Folder 6)
    - SUNY Academic Recall Study [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1990 June (Box III.5.13, Folder 7)
    - SUNY-Access [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1991 December (Box III.5.13, Folder 8)
    - SUNY-Advocacy Plan [RESTRICTED], 1992 September (Box III.5.13, Folder 9)
    - SUNY-Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1977-1990 (Box III.5.13, Folder 10)
    - SUNY-Affirmative Action [RESTRICTED], 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box III.5.13, Folder 11-12)
    - SUNY's Best Program [RESTRICTED], 1987 October-1990 October; 1991 October-1992 July; 2 folders (Box III.5.13, Folder 13-14)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1987 September-1987 November (Box III.5.13, Folder 15)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1988 March (Box III.5.13, Folder 16)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 February-1988 September (Box III.5.13, Folder 17)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1988 November (Box III.5.13, Folder 18)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1988 December (Box III.5.13, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1989 February (Box III.5.13, Folder 20)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 February-1989 March (Box III.5.13, Folder 21)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 March-1989 June (Box III.5.13, Folder 22)
    - SUNY Budget-Board of Trustees [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box III.5.13, Folder 23)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 1 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.13, Folder 24)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 2 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.13, Folder 25)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 3 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.14, Folder 1)
    - SUNY Budget-Clippings, etc. (folder 4 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June (Box III.5.14, Folder 2)
    - SUNY Budget-Campus Questionnaires budget cut plans impact [RESTRICTED], 1989 January-1989 March; 2 folders (Box III.5.14, Folder 3-4)
    - SUNY Budget-Campaign (letter writing to legislators, etc) [RESTRICTED], 1988 November-1989 June; 2 folders (Box III.5.14, Folder 5-6)
    - SUNY Budget Crisis [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 December; 1989 October (Box III.5.14, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Budget-Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1989 May (Box III.5.14, Folder 8)
    - SUNY Budget-Mailings to Members [RESTRICTED], 1988 October-1989 March (Box III.5.14, Folder 9)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1989 July-1989 December (Box III.5.14, Folder 10)
    - SUNY Budget 90-91 [RESTRICTED], 1990 January-1990 March; 2 folders (Box III.5.14, Folder 11-12)
    - SUNY Budget 1990 [RESTRICTED], 1990 May (Box III.5.14, Folder 13)
    - SUNY Budget-Campus Budget Reports [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box III.5.14, Folder 14)
    - SUNY Budget [RESTRICTED], 1991 July-1992 April (Box III.5.14, Folder 15)
    - SUNY-Buffalo Proposal [re: research group in education?] [RESTRICTED], 1988 June (Box III.5.14, Folder 16)
    - SUNY-Chancellor [RESTRICTED], 1990 December-1993 April (Box III.5.14, Folder 17)
    - SUNY Committee on Institutional Performance [RESTRICTED], 1988 January-1988 May (Box III.5.14, Folder 18)
    - SUNY-Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1992 March-1993 April (Box III.5.14, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Disability Program [RESTRICTED], 1985-1988 (Box III.5.14, Folder 20)
    - SUNY Faculty Senate [RESTRICTED], 1992 January (Box III.5.14, Folder 21)
    - SUNY-Faculty Utilization [RESTRICTED], 1991-1992 (Box III.5.14, Folder 22)
    - SUNY's Future: Expanding the Mission, Fulfilling the Promise, letters regarding [RESTRICTED], 1990 April-1990 May (Box III.5.14, Folder 23)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring [RESTRICTED], 1986 February-1991 September (Box III.5.14, Folder 24)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring [RESTRICTED], 1991-January 1992; 3 folders (Box III.5.14, Folder 25-27)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring/Hospital Employees Survey [RESTRICTED], 1991 January-1993 March (Box III.5.14, Folder 28)
    - SUNY Hospital Restructuring Workshop [RESTRICTED], 1993 April-1993 May (Box III.5.14, Folder 29)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 1 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.14, Folder 30)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 2 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.14, Folder 31)
    - SUNY Hospitals (folder 3 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box III.5.15, Folder 1)
    - SUNY-Meeting with J. Burke (Provost) [RESTRICTED], 1993 May 4; 1993 April-1993 May (Box III.5.15, Folder 2)
    - SUNY Patent Policy [RESTRICTED], 1986 October-1988 September (Box III.5.15, Folder 3)
    - SUNY Productivity [RESTRICTED], 1993 February (Box III.5.15, Folder 4)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 June (Box III.5.15, Folder 5)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 August (Box III.5.15, Folder 6)
    - SUNY-State Revenue Shortfall [RESTRICTED], 1988 August-1988 October (Box III.5.15, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1987 May-1987 June; 1989 March-1989 November (Box III.5.15, Folder 8)
    - SUNY Statistical Releases [RESTRICTED], 1987 December-1988 June (Box III.5.15, Folder 9)
    - SUNY Statistical Releases [RESTRICTED], 1988 June-1988 December (Box III.5.15, Folder 10)
    - SUNY Women's Conference [RESTRICTED], 1990 August-1990 November (Box III.5.15, Folder 11)
    - SUNY Workload [RESTRICTED], 1991 September-1992 July (Box III.5.15, Folder 12)
    - SUNYSAT [RESTRICTED], 1988 March-1988 August (Box III.5.15, Folder 13)
    - Teacher Centers [RESTRICTED], 1986-1988 (Box III.5.15, Folder 14)